Sparks Photographs
undated
- Photographs, 1860-1997
  - Two women with tennis rackets, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_618; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two women standing outside. One is holding sunglasses in her hand and the other is holding a tennis racket and tennis balls. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California.
  - Man and woman standing in front of barracks at Camp Elliott, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_619; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a man and woman standing on asphalt. In the background is a two story building. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Man and woman in uniform standing in front of some buildings, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_620; Photographic print; 3 5/8 x 2 5/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a man and woman in military dress. Behind them are two houses. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Group of people standing outside, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_621; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 2 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of six women and one man standing outside. There are two buildings in the background. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Four bicyclists talking with two people in military uniform, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_622; Photographic print; 3 5/8 x 2 5/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of four women on bicycles talking with a man and woman in military dress. In the background are some two story buildings. The man and woman in military dress are the same as in photo 00620. The woman no the right with her hand in the air is most likely Nancy Lee Sparks. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California.
  - Group of Navy soldiers, Undated; UNRS-P2017-13_623; Photographic print; 3 3/8 x 2 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of fifteen men in Navy uniforms standing in two rows. They are all looking up at the camera. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California.
  - Single story building with a telephone pole, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_624; Photographic print; 3 x 1 1/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a single story building with a telephone pole in front of it. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California.
  - Three men playing golf, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_625; Photographic print; 2 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of three men holding golf clubs standing on a grassy field. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Group of people standing between two buildings, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_626; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 3 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of six women and one man standing for a photo. They are between two buildings. The woman second from the left in the front road may be Nancy Lee Sparks. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California.
  - Seven people with bicycles, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_627; Photographic print; 3 3/8 x 2 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of four women and three men in front of a fence. The women and two of the men are all on bicycles. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Three men standing outside, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_628; Photographic print; 3 3/8 x 2 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of three men standing in front of a fence. The man on the left is holding the chin of the man in the middle. The man in the middle is resting his arms on the other two men's shoulders. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identificaiton.
  - Two women sitting by a building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_629; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two women sitting next to a building. One has two small bags in her lap. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Three women at the bottom of a staircase, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_630; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 3 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of three women on a staircase outside of a building. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Two women standing at the bottom of a staircase, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_631; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two women standing at the bottom of a staircase. There is a U. S. Navy truck parked in the background. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Two untidy bunks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_632; Photographic print; 4 3/8 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two untidy bunks in a room. There is a smudge in the center of the photograph obscuring some of the photo. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California.
  - Woman in military uniform standing outside, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_633; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman in a white military uniform standing outside. She is holding a folder in her hand. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Woman in uniform holding a parcel in front of a porch, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_634; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman in military dress standing on a staircase leading to a porch. She is holding a sheet of paper in her hands. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Woman in uniform walking away, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_635; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman in a military uniform walking along a road. She is holding a folder in her hand. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
    Located in an album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover. The leaves of the album have been unscrewed from the cover and left in original order. Same woman as in photo 00633.
  - Two men and a woman outside a building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_636; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two men and one woman standing in front of a building with their arms wrapped around each other. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identification.
  - Three women and two men outside a building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_637; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two men and three women in military uniform. They are standing in front of a building. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California. No identificaiton.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks standing outside some buildings, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_638; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks in military dress standing in front of a building. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks and three friends, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_639; Photographic print; 5 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of four women in military dress standing in front of a couple buildings. The woman second from the right is Nancy Lee Sparks. Most likely taken at Camp Elliott, San Diego, California.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks sitting on a bench, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_640; Photographic print; 3 1/8 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks sitting on a bench in front of a chain link fence. She is wearing a white baseball cap, shorts, and a white shirt.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks playing tennis, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_641; Photographic print; 3 1/8 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks holding a tennis racket on a tennis court. She is wearing a white baseball cap, shorts, and a white shirt.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, Laurine Bergin, and two other school teachers, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_642; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 3 1/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of four women standing in a hallway. Nancy Lee Sparks is standing second from the right while Mrs. Laurine Bergin is second from the left.
    Located in an album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover. The leaves of the album have been unscrewed from the cover and left in original order. Same women photo as in photo 00646.
  - Laurine Bergin, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_643; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 2 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman sitting on a ledge outside of a building. The woman is Mrs. Laurine Bergin, who is also in photo 00647.
  - Woman lying in grass, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_644; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 2 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman lying on the grass. She has a bandana wrapped around her head to keep her hair back. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_645; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 2 1/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks outside of a building. There are short bushes behind her.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, Laurine Bergin, and two other school teachers, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_646; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 3 1/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of four women standing in a hallway. Laurine Bergin is on the left and Nancy Lee Sparks is on the right.
    Located in an album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover. The leaves of the album have been unscrewed from the cover and left in original order. Same women as in photo 00642.
  - Mrs. Kreutzman, Nancy Lee Sparks, Laurine Bergin, and Miss Sivicegood, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_647; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 5 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Photograph of four women standing in front of a fence smiling and laughing. Handwritten on verso: June 1947 Mrs. Kreutzman, Miss Sparks, Mrs. Bergin, Miss Sivicegood taken by Hermima Ross.
    Photograph was loose in the album, removed, and sleeved.
  - Talent show at the City College of San Francisco, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_648; Photographic print; 6 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a group of people on stage, possibly for a talent or variety show. The front row is holding a sign which says City College of San Francisco. In front of the sign is a person in a horse costume. No identification.
  - Dance number for a show at the City College of San Francisco, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_649; Photographic print; 6 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a group of people dancing on a stage for a show put on by the City College of San Francisco. Written on front: 185. No identification.
  - Show at the City College of San Francisco, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_650; Photographic print; 6 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a group of people on stage for a show put on by the City College of San Francisco. No identification.
  - Play at the City College of San Francisco, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_651; Photographic print; 6 3/4 x 4 5/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of people dancing on stage. There is a man playing an upright piano with the letters CCSF on the front (most likely for City College of San Francisco). Above the stage are the iconic drama masks (happy and sad). No identification.
  - People dancing on a stage at City College of San Francisco, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_652; Photographic print; 6 5/8 x 4 3/4 (Box 11)
    A dark photograph of people dancing on a stage, most likely at the City College of San Francisco. No identification.
  - People dancing on a stage at the City College of San Francisco, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_653; Photographic print; 6 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a group of people dancing on a stage. There are the iconic drama masks above the stage, and musicians in a pit orchestra below the stage. Most likely a performance put on at the City College of San Francisco. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks and Miss Sivicegood standing outside, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_654; Photographic print; 7 x 5 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks and Miss Sivicegood outside. Sparks has a whistle around her neck.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks and Miss Sivicegood, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_655; Photographic print; 7 x 5 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks and an Miss Sivicegood standing outside. Sparks has a whistle around her neck.
  - Building with a shingle roof and a domed bell tower, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_656; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a stone building with a shingled roof and a curved bell tower.
  - Woman standing in a stone archway, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_657; Photographic print; 1 7/8 x 3 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman standing in a stone archway. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks standing next to a water spout, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_658; Photographic print; 1 3/4 x 3 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks standing in front of a stone building with a barred window. She is bending over next to a water pump faucet.
  - Road leading toward some buildings, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_659; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a road leading to some single story buildings. There are some hills in the background.
  - Stone church and building with cars parked in front of it, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_660; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a stone church, a white building, and some cars parked in the distance.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks and three friends outside Helen Carter Dresses, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_661; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of four women standing outside a building which has painted by the door "Helen Carter Dresses." Nancy Lee Sparks is second from the right.
  - Woman standing behind a barred window in a stone building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_662; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman standing in a barred window of a stone building. No identification.
  - Three women standing in front of a car, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_663; Photographic print; 4 5/8 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of three women standing in front of a car. There are trees in the background. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks and two women in front of a house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_664; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of three women standing in front of a single story house. Nancy Lee Sparks is on the left.
  - Woman sitting facing away from the camera, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_665; Photographic print; 2 3/8 x 4 1/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman with her back to the camera. She is sitting on the ground. No identification.
  - Woman smiling at the camera, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_666; Photographic print; 2 3/8 x 4 1/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman in a striped shirt sitting on the ground. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_667; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 3 1/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks standing in front of trees. She is wearing a blouse, cardigan, and a cap.
  - Woman looking over a car window wearing a visor, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_668; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 3 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman wearing a visor looking over the edge of a car window. No identification.
  - Woman standing by a house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_669; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman standing by the edge of a building with trees and a car in the background. No identification.
  - Woman brushing her hair back, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_670; Photogaphic print; 4 5/8 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman standing with a house and cars on the street behind her. No identification.
  - Two women in shorts standing on a lawn, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_671; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two women in shorts standing on a front lawn with a house across the street in the background. No identification.
  - Woman next to a slightly ajar door, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_672; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman standing next to a door labeled 14, which is slightly ajar. The woman is also in photos 00671 and 00674. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks wearing a bandanna and shorts, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_673; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks wearing shorts, a shirt, and a bandanna wrapped around her head. There is a street with a car behind her.
  - Woman standing next to a metal railing, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_674; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman standing next to a railing. There is a door ajar in the background which is labeled 14. No identification. The same woman as in photos 00671 and 00672.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks on a mountainside next to snow, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_675; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks standing on a mountainside. She is standing at the edge of snow and there are evergreen trees in the background.
  - Woman standing in a field, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_676; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman standing in a field with some evergreen trees behind her. There is a mountain in the background. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks walking through snow, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_677; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks walking through snow on the side of a mountain.
  - Snow covered town, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_678; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a town which has snow on the ground around it.
    Located in an album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover. The leaves of the album have been unscrewed from the cover and left in original order. Captions on this album page do not correspond with the photos.
  - Water wheel, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_679; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a water wheel surrounded by trees.
  - Mountain side partially covered in snow, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_680; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a mountain side partially covered in snow.
  - Small buildings surrounded by trees, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_681; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two small buildings with trees and a barn behind them.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks and a man standing in front of a car, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_682; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks standing next to a man in front of a car. There is a palm tree and a house in the background.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks standing next to a boulder, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_683; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks standing next to a boulder. In the background are some ridges and mountains.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks looking over a canyon landscape, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_684; Photographic print; 2 7/8 x 3 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman (possibly Nancy Lee Sparks) standing at the edge of a ridge looking out over the landscape. In the background are some mountains covered with trees.
  - Inside of a greenhouse, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_685; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of the inside of a greenhouse covered in plants.
  - Two story building with an exterior case, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_686; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a two story building with a staircase curving up to the second floor on the right side. There are trees in the background.
  - Unidentified elderly man in a kilt, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_687; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a man with a kilt, cap, and a plaid cloak. He is standing on a road with a view of a valley behind him. No identification.
  - Two buildings surrounded by trees, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_688; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two buildings with trees behind them. One of the buildings is a single story and the other is two stories.
  - Blurry photo of a house with a fence, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_689; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Blurry photograph of the front of a house with a fence and trees in front.
  - Front entrance of a house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_690; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of the front of a house. The walkway has bushes and ivy on either side.
  - Allie Burwitz in a greenhouse, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_691; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Allie Burwitz Sparks standing in a greenhouse wearing a floral pattern dress.
  - Allie Burwitz in a greenhouse, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_692; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
  - Two elderly women holding handbags, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_693; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two elderly women carrying handbags standing in front of a brick house. No identification.
  - Woman sitting on a front porch, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_694; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman sitting on a front porch. One of the columns on the porch has the address 226. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks and another woman holding handbags, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_695; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of an elderly woman and Nancy Lee Sparks holding handbags. They are standing in front of a brick house.
  - Man and woman standing on a sidewalk in front of a car, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_696; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a man and woman standing on a sidewalk. There is a tree and car behind them. No identification.
    Located in an album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover. The leaves of the album have been unscrewed from the cover and left in original order. Caption on album page does not correspond with the photos on the page.
  - A man and woman standing under a tree, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_697; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 4 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a young man and woman standing in front of a tree on a front lawn. There are two people leaning against a car on the street. No identification.
  - Young man standing on a lawn, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_698; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 4 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a young man standing on the front lawn of a single story house. No identification.
  - Man, two girls, and a boy with a bicycle, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_699; Photographic print; 4 3/8 x 2 5/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a man, woman, boy, and girl on a sidewalk. The boy is leaning on a bicycle and there are two cars on the street behind them. No identification.
  - Boy with a bicycle and a girl, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_700; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of the boy and girl from photo 00699 standing on a front lawn with a bicycle. There is a car and house in the background. No identification.
  - Boy in a football uniform throwing a football, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_701; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a boy in a football uniform which is labeled number 10. He is about to throw a football. No identification.
  - Portrait of an unidentified woman, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_702; Photographic print; 3 7/8 x 4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a portrait of a young girl wearing a string of pearls around her neck. No identification.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks in a garden, August 1959; UNRS-P2017-13_703; Photographic print; 3 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks standing among plants outside of a house.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks sitting in a chair in the courtyard, August 1959; UNRS-P2017-13_704; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks sitting in a chair in an open courtyard. There is a plant behind her.
  - Man and woman on or under ladder with Nancy Lee Sparks, August 1959; UNRS-P2017-13_705; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)